sportposting.com 2010-09-06

# Sportposting.com "Watch" "Play" "Train"::Privacy

Protecting your privacy is very important to our website. We will not sell, lease or exchange your personal data to third parties without first obtaining your express consent.

This privacy policy describes how we collect and use your data. If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy policy or its enforcement, please feel free to contact administrator.

Sportposting is an online social networking community that connects people through member posted sporting events. Members create their own profiles, and those profiles are accessible through the site, unless the exact url were to be typed in; profile url are kept secret and are not accesible by other members.

Sportposting collects information our users submit to us such as their name and e-mail address to allow us to identify users and notify them of changes or updates to our service. We also collect personal information submitted by our users in filling out their profile on the service such as gender, location, age, etc. We collect this personal information when our users: sign up as a member; make changes to their member profile information; and send e-mail messages. Members may choose to provide additional information beyond their basic profile for their other profile sections. Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional, but enables our users to better identify each other and more effectively connect and interact with their network. 

Like many other Web sites, Sportposting uses a standard technology called "cookies." Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive - not on our site. They can help make the Internet experience quicker and more convenient. Cookies allow our users to login without entering their ID and password each time they use Sportposting. Members who disable cookies will not be able to use Sportposting. 

Email address and full name are displayed only when a user requests to add another user to their Sportposting list, and when we send notifications to a user related to their use of the service. Except when members invite friends, full names are not shared or displayed with people outside of their Personal Network. Email addresses of Sportposting members are never displayed to other users on the system. Users within a Personal Network communicate on Sportposting with each other through the Sportposting service without disclosing their email addresses.

We will not sell, lease or exchange your personal data to third parties without first obtaining your express consent, unless required by law or to protect your membership. 

If you use our Invite feature to invite a friend to our service, we will ask you for your friend's email address. We'll automatically send the friend an email inviting them to join, as well as two reminder messages. Sportposting does not sell these email addresses or use them to transmit any communication other than the invitation and reminders to join your personal Network. Sportposting stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this invitation and reminders, and for tracking the success of our Invite functionality.

The Sportposting site may contain links to other Web sites. Please be aware that Sportposting is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites our users choose to visit. If our users provide any information directly to parties other than Sportposting, different rules may apply to the use or disclosure of the personal information disclosed. We encourage you to investigate and ask questions before disclosing your personal information to third parties. 

Please be aware that whenever members voluntarily disclose personal information online - e.g., file uploads, image uploads adn events- that information becomes public and can be collected and used by others. By posting personal information online in events, members may receive unsolicited messages from other parties.
